I never suspected that the Light Music Club
もうすぐ学園祭というこの時期に
would face a crisis of these proportions so soon before the School Festival.
まさか 軽音部にこんな危機が訪れるとは 思っていませんでした
You sure are in a good mood, Azusa.
なんか ご機嫌だな 梓
えッ？
I get happy when I think about actually playing a live show at the festival.
もうすぐ学祭で ライブができると思うと
うれしくて
Oh, that's really cute!
初々しいね～
I wish I could see you play at last year's festival.
去年の軽音部のライブも見たかったです
Yeah, guess you put on a pretty big show last year, didn't you, Mio?
澪は去年 大活躍だったもんな
えッ？
She tripped while she was up on stage--
ステージで転んで…
うわ～ッ！
Hey, I just happen to have a recording of their last year show.
去年の学園祭のライブなら ちゃんと撮ってあるわよ
I wanna see! I wanna see!
見たいです 見たいです
Are you sure you won't reconsider, Azusa?
いや梓 考え直さない？
Yui, Ritsu.
唯ちゃん りっちゃん
Wait! No. Let go...
は～ な～ せ～
Now, let's start with the primo scene.
それじゃ オススメシーンから
Don't look, Azusa! It's too dangerous! You'll be cursed!
やめろ梓
危険だぞ 呪われるぞ
シマシマ～
見… 見ちゃいました
I can't unsee it.
I was too late...
遅かった
CHATTING NOW
Chatting Now
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
No no!
study
hard
精一杯Study After School
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
we can fly
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
Further than yesterday
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Jumping
now
Jumping Now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never     Ending
Girls'     Life
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
Even if we
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
No no!
Shouting with all
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
We'll
sing
for
you
歌えばShining After School
After school
Crisis!
It's pretty weird.
それにしても
You guys seem to only play incredibly well during live performances.
ライブのときだけは みなさん すごい演奏してますよね
Oh, look at you, offering up opinions and everything!
言うようになったな～ この～
Head lock!
What is it, Yui?
えッ 何？
This is bringing back a lot of fun memories.
なんか いろいろ思い出して
As I recall, you grew out (of) your voice just before we did this show.
ああ 確かこのとき 唯ちゃん 声が
Yeah!
My voice was all scratchy when I woke up that morning.
そうそう 朝起きたら 声ガラガラなんだもん
That's right. So Mio took over--
それて澪ちゃんの代わりにボーカルやって
This would be your first show as a member of the Light Music Club.
梓にとっちゃ 軽音部として初ライブだな
--singing was really good!
でもよかったよね　澪ちゃんの歌
Yeah! I'm gonna give it all I've got!
はい 私 頑張ります
うん　なんと素晴らしかった
カッコよかったな～　ホント～
Sorry to interrupt when you're having such a good time.
盛り上がってるとこ 悪いんだけど
Oh, Nodoka! What's going on?
ああ 和 どうしたの？
Don't act like you don't know. This!
どうしたのじゃないのよ これ
Auditorium Use Application...
講堂使用届
Right. You haven't submitted one for the School Festival.
そう 学祭の分 出してないでしょ
Oh, I completely forgot.
ああ 忘れてた
Don't be so nonchalant!
そんな のんきな
Things've been kinda hectic, so it slipped my mind.
いや～ 忙しくってね
The same thing happened last year.
去年にも こんなことあったな
Actually, that was the Club Application...
ああ あれは部活申請…
Ow!
痛ッ
Okay, Azusa, you be the secretary.
ああ… じゃあ梓 書記な
Me? Well, I guess I don't mind.
えッ 私？
まあ いいですけど
Let's see, "Applicant" is Light Music Club...
えっと 使用者は「軽音部」
So, what do I put down for Name?
あの 名称って？
The band name, I guess.
バンド名で いいんじゃない？
Right.
はい…
あッ そういえば バンド名って何でしたっけ？
Now that you mention it, what is the band's name?
The Girls Gang!
Smile and Sweets!
Chocolate Melody!
「スイーツ·スマイル」
「ちょこれーと·めろでぃ」
「恩那組」
They're all different!
バラバラ…
We never settled on one.
決めてなかったね
Then it's the perfect time to pick a name!
いい機会だから 決めるか
I got it! How about "Yui Hirasawa and the Bumbling Sisters?"
「平沢唯と ずっこけシスターズ」って どう？
What are we, chopped liver?
私ら 何もんだ！
How about something like "Pure Pure"?
「ぴゅあ·ぴゅあ」とか どうかな
Ah, enough with the jokes, let's be serious about this.
もう ネタはいいから マジメに考えようぜ
But I was being serious...
わりと本気なのに…
You really meant that?!
本気だったんかい
Well, everyone has different tastes. Doesn't make that wrong?
ほら 人のセンスはいろいろですから
All right, then!
よ～し わかった
I'll choose the band name!
私が決める
I think we should all give it a little more thought!
もう少しみんなで考えよう
They pulled together...
団結した
Just bring the paperwork to the Student Council Office when you're done.
じゃあ 書類 あとで生徒会室に持ってきてね
I'm sorry we made you wait for nothing.
悪いな 待たせちゃって
It's all right.
いいよ
Nodoka-chan, why don't you and I stop'n grab some tea on the way home?
和ちゃん たまには帰りに お茶しようよ
Sure, Yui, I'll text you later.
わかった あとでメールする
Okay, why don't we all just sleep on the band name tonight and get to practicing our set for the show now?
まあ じゃあバンド名は各自ひと晩考えてくることにして
練習するか
I agree.
そうね
The Festival's soon, so we have to give it 110%.
学園祭も近いんだから 気合い入れないとな
I will!
はい
Oh, sound!
あッ そうだ
My guitar hasn't really been sounding quite right lately.
なんか 最近 音の調子悪くて
えッ？
You want me to take a quick look at it?
ちょっと見せてもらえますか？
うッ…弦 さびてるじゃないですか
These strings are all corroded!
When was the last time you changed them out for new ones, Yui?
これ いつ弦を交換したんですか？
Huh? You mean you're supposed to change the strings?
えッ 弦って交換するものなの？
なッ 何!?
What?
Plus, the neck is warped.
ていうか… ネックも反ってるし
Didn't you know that a warped guitar neck can completely throw off the octave tuning!
これだと オクターブ·チューニングも めちゃくちゃですよ
オ オクタ… ネック？
Neck? Octa...?
Calm down, Azusa!
落ち着け 梓
This is way too much for Yui to digest!
今の唯には到底 理解できない
Basically, you have to take really good care of your instrument.
つまり… 大事にしないと ダメじゃないですか
This is a beautiful guitar!
いいギターなのに
But I do take good care of it!
大事にしてるもん！
I sleep with it every night, I dress it up nice!
一緒に寝たりとか 服着せたりとか
That's not what I mean by ‘taking care of it!'
大事にするベクトルが違います
ええ？ じゃあ…
In that case, is there anything you can do to fix it, Miss Yamanaka?
さわちゃん先生 なんとかしてよ～
I think you'd be better off taking it to the music store, don't you?
やっぱり お店に頼んだほうが いいんじゃない？
You just can't be bothered.
めんどくさいだけだろ
You and I better just go to the music store, then.
じゃあ 楽器店に行きましょうか
It isn't that serious, is it?
えッ そこまでしなくても…
The festival's coming up, and we can't practice with your guitar and the shape it's in!
いや 学園祭も近いのに これじゃ練習になりませんよ
うん…
Ritchan, you don't do any upkeep on your drums, do you?
りっちゃんも お手入れなんか してないよね？
Yes, I do!
しとるわい
えッ？
And even if I didn't, don't make it sound like a foregone conclusion that I don't.
私はしてなくても当たり前みたいな聞き方するな
It is you we're talking about...
りっちゃんのくせに
Ow!
痛てッ
Okay, here we are.
はいは～い 到着
Hey, I'll wait for you guys out here, okay?
じゃ 私ここで待ってるから
But, why aren't you coming inside?
えッ 何でですか？
You see the thing is I'm a lefty,
私 左利きだから
so looking at all those right handed instruments would only make me sad.
右利き用の楽器 見ても 悲しくなるだけだし
ああ…
あッ でも ほら澪
Hey, Mio! Check this out!
It says here that they're having a Lefty Fair today.
何か レフティ·フェアやってるよ
えッ!?
こ… ここは天国ですか！
Have I died and gone to heaven?
うわ…
Clerk! I want you to give me everything you have on display here!
てん… 店員さん ここにあるの 全部ください
Hey, Mio, get a grip, girl.
こら 落ち着け
Boy, Mio-chan sure looks happy.
澪ちゃん 楽しそう
That's 'cause there's not a lot of models made for lefties.
左利き用は少ないですから
So you wanna just go on without them?
先 行ってましょうか
Mm-hmm.
うん
Excuse us!
すいませ～ん
How can I help you?
いらっしゃいませ
We were wandering if you could make some adjustment on a guitar for us.
ギターの調整してもらいたいんですけど
Yeah, sure thing. On which guitar?
はい どちらのですか？
This one.
こちらの
Ah. Well, why don't we have a look at it and see what we've got.
ああ では ちょっと見せてもらいますね
Um, is this a vintage guitar?
あの… これ…ビンテージギターですか？
No, we're sorry. It's just kinda dirty. That's all.
すいません ただ汚いだけです
It's been a year since I bought it!
まだ買って１年です
I-I see...
は はあ…
Well, feel free to wait in the store until I'm finished with it.
それじゃあ 終わるまで 店内でお待ちください
Thank you very much.
お願いします
Well, let's browse around the store until he's done.
じゃあ 終わるまで 何か見てましょうか
Hey, what's the matter, Yui?
どうしたんですか？
ジー
ああ… 私のギターが裸にされてゆく…
My poor guitar is being stripped naked bit by bit!
What are you talking about?
何言ってんですか
I'm curious about something, Yui? Why did you buy that guitar in the first place?
でも 何で唯先輩は あのギター買ったんですか？
うん？
I mean, look at it. It's heavy, and it's got a thick neck.
ほら 重いし ネックは太いし
It's got all sorts of quirks.
クセがあるじゃないですか
Huh? I got it because it's cute!
あッ だって かわいいから
Because it's cute?
かわいい？
Yeah, that's right.
かわいいから
えッ かわいいよね　かわいくない？
You do think it's cute, don't you, Azu-nyan?
I just don't get Yui-senpai's tastes.
唯先輩の感覚は わからない
Sorry we kept you waiting!
お待たせしました
おう
We dropped it off to have them do some maintenance.
メンテナンス 頼んできました
Right, good deal.
お疲れ
Wait a minute. Where did Mio-senpai go?
あれ 澪先輩は？
Oh, Mio is still over there checking out--
ああ　澪ちゃんなら　まだ…
Miss Kotobuki!
紬お嬢様
It's so good to see you again, Miss!
いらっしゃいませ お嬢様
Oh, hello.
ああ どうも
Hey! If it isn't Miss Kotobuki! It's been way too long!
これは 紬お嬢様 お久しぶりです
Mugi says that this shop is part of her family's business consortium.
ここ ムギんちの系列の楽器店なんだってよ
今日はどのようなご用件で？
ああ 友達の付き添いです
えッ？
It's always a shock to hear someone call her that, isn't it?
それはそれは お疲れです
ビックリするんだよね あの呼び方
いえいえ
Thank you for waiting.
お待たせしました
おう
ああ
わあ キレイになったな～
It's all clean again!
Make sure you keep it maintained from now on.
これからは こまめにメンテナンスをして…
Geeta!
ギー太！
She named the thing...
名前つけてたんだ
Oh, thank you so much, sir!
ありがとうございました
Don't mention it.
い いえ…
So, ah, the bill comes to $50.
ああ お代のほう 5000円になります
Huh?
えッ？
You charge for this?
お金取るの？
Um, y-yes.
えッ ええ…
Well, of course they charge for it!
いや 当たり前ですよ
I have no money.
お金ない
えッ!?
What do I do?
どうしよう…
What's the matter?
どうしたの？
Well, it looks like Yui-senpai didn't know that music stores charge for maintenance work.
いいえ 唯先輩 メンテナンスにお金かかるって 知らなかったみたいで
Oh, she didn't, huh? Oh, goodness.
えッ そうなの？ どうしよう
Did I bring any pocket money?
手持ち あったかしら
O-Oh, M-Miss, no!
おおお… お嬢様
Perish the thought! Consider it on the house!
ここはサービスということで
No, I couldn't possibly!
そんな 悪いわ
とんでもない
Please, think nothing of it! We're constantly in your father's debt!
日ごろ お父様にお世話になっていますので
B-But I...
えッ でも…
I insist! Please, this is on the house!
Well, it looks like you just lucked out.
いえ　ここは是非サービスさせてください
なんとか なったみたいだな
That's that, then! What do you say we all get going?
それじゃあ そろそろ帰りますか
Yeah!
は～い
て あれ？
うん？
Aren't we forgetting Mio-senpai?
あの 澪先輩が…
Yeah, I'll go call her.
ああ… 呼んでくるわ
Mio! Come on, it's time to go.
澪 ほら 帰るぞ
Don't wanna.
ヤダ
Are you a grade schooler?
小学生か
Look, everybody's waiting for you and we have to get back.
てゆ～か みんな待ってんだって
Don't wanna.
ヤダ
Sheesh!
もお～
Come on, Mio, let's go!
ほ～ら 澪ちゃん
Hey! Ritsu!
ちょ… 律
It's time to go home now, Mio.
はいは～い 帰りまちょ～ね
I know this one person who actually likes to string his guitar in reverse order.
I said I don't wanna go!
ヤダってば もう
知り合いの方は 弦を逆に張り替えて使ってましたけど
ダ～メ ほら 行くぞ
Wha...
ちょッ あッ あぶなッ！
へえ～
Hey, wait! Watch it! Ow!
Hey, what'cha doing down there, Mio?
何やってんだよ～ 澪
Enough, already!
もういいよ
えッ？
You jerk.
バカ律
Thank goodness, Geeta is all pretty again!
よかった～ ギー太キレイになって
You gave your guitar a name, huh? That's nice.
名前つけてたんだな それ
So, what do you want to do now?
このあと どうする？
う～ん そうだな
Good question...
Hey, how about going for tea?!
よし お茶でも飲んでくか
Tea again? Really?
また お茶ですか？
Sorry, guys!
あッ ごめん
But I'm supposed to get together with Nodoka-chan right now.
私このあと 和ちゃんと約束あるんだ
え～？
えッ 和もくるの？
You gonna see Nodoka? Can I tag along?
私も行っていい？
Oh, that's right! You and Nodoka-chan are in the same class together, aren't you?
あそっか
澪ちゃん 和ちゃんと同じクラスだもんね
Sure.
いいよ～
Really?
ホント！
I'm just gonna give her a call and let her know you're coming.
じゃあ 和ちゃんにも連絡するね
Great, thanks!
うん ありがとう
けいおん！
うわ～ ここ 一度きてみたかったんだ
Oh, I've always wanted to try out this place!
But you have no money?
お金ないのに？
It's okay. I'll pay for Yui's share.
唯の分は 私が出すわ
When I get next month's allowance, we'll all go out and it'll all be on me, how's that?!
来月のお小遣い入ったら 今度は私がごちそうするもん
I'll hold you to that.
お願いするわ
So, is Yui really doing all right at the Light Music Club like she says?
こんなんで唯 うまくやってけてるのかしら 軽音部
Yeah! But whenever she learns one thing, she has a tendency to completely forget something else.
それが １つのことを覚えたら １つのことを忘れちゃって
I know how it is.
ああ あるある
But when she's focused on something, she can do amazing things.
一度やり出したら すごいとこまでいくんだけどね
That's for sure.
そうそう
She can be a real handful, can't she?
やっぱり苦労するんだよね
Huh? What'cha talking about?
えッ 何 何？
Duh! Those two sure seem to be having a good time together.
ちッ 何かいい雰囲気だな あの２人
More to the point, why are we sneaking around like this?
ていうか 何で こんなコソコソと
It's like for private investigators, isn't it?
何か 探偵さんみたいね
That's it! I'm going in.
よし 突撃
えッ？
And then the teacher came up to me and--
それで あの先生さ…
Well, you two sure seem really friendly!
お２人さん 仲いっすね～
Hey!
Ritsu? What are you doing here?
律 何でここに？
Oh, I just happened to be here.
いや～ たまたまね
Did you come here all by yourself?
あれ りっちゃん１人？
Nope, Mugi and Azusa are sitting over there.
ああ ムギたちは そっちにいるよ
Huh? Oh, hey, there they are!
あッ ホントだ
Oh, gosh! Thank you for taking such good care of our little Mio!
いや～ ウチの澪が いつもお世話になってま～す
Ritsu?
ちょ… 律
うん 何 何かヤなの？
What? You want me to leave?
Well, no, I don't, but I…
いや そうじゃないけど
Then what's the problem?
だったら いいじゃん
What's she doing?
りっちゃん
なに　なに頼んでんの？
What's that? What did you get?
アイス 溶けちゃうのに
Her ice cream is melting...
Wow, that's a gorgeous boxed lunch!
うわ～ キレイなお弁当
No, it's not. I just threw together whatever I had lying around. I just put together what I had.
そんなことないよ あり合わせの物 詰めただけだし
えッ 自分で作ってるんだ すご～い
You mean you make your own? That's amazing!
Oh, come on. It's no big deal, really.
やだな そんなことないってば
No, mine are always--
ううん 私なんて…
Okay, lunchtime is over!
はい ランチタイム終了
えッ 律
Ritsu?
Sorry, but I just started eating.
いや 私は今から…
We're practicing through every lunch break from now until the school festival!
これから学祭までは 昼休みも練習するから
えッ
Gee, I wonder what Mio's gonna do to liven things up at this year's big school festival concert?
いや～ 今年の学園祭は
澪 どんなふうに盛り上げてくれんのかな～
She gave the crowd that panty shot last year,
去年はパンチラだったし～
so maybe she'll show them her belly button this time?
今年は ヘソ出しとかかな
あッ それとも…
Or maybe--
I thought we were gonna practice!
練習するんだろ！
するよ～
And we will!
だったら…
Then why are you--
Takoyaki!
たこ焼き～
Huh?
はあ？
Ponytail!
ポニーテール～
Hey!
ちょ…
Braids!
三つ編み
Come on, cut it out!
ちょっと やめろって
もう なんなんだよ
What's gotten into you?
あッ そうそう オススメのすっごい怖いホラー映画 持ってきたんだけど
Oh, guess what I brought! A great horror movie! So scary, It'll make your hair stand up.
This is stupid. I'm going back to my classroom.
もッ もう 教室戻るぞ
All right. Suit yourself.
ふ～ん 戻れば
Gosh, I'm so sorry I interrupted your wonderfully pleasant lunchtime with Nodoka, your brand new best friend.
悪かったよ せっかくの和との楽しいランチタイムを邪魔してさ
Who said anything about that?!
そんなこと言ってないだろ！
I don't get it why they're fighting?
何 どうしたんだろ
How about some tea? Let's have some tea!
お お茶にしない？
お茶にしよう…
All right? I brought some lovely tarts today.
ねッ 今日 美味しいタルト持って来てて
What should I do?
どッ どうしよう
I have to do something! Anything!
All right?
ねッ？
何とかしなきゃ 何とか…
みッ みなさん 仲よく練習しましょう…
Let's all be friends and practice together like we planned!
I-It didn't work!
はッ はずした
Yeah, I guess we should practice.
まあ 練習するか
うん やろっか
Let's get started.
S-Sure! All right!
あッ はい
One, two!
ワン ツー
あれ？
Ritsu?
律
What gives? I'm glad that your drumming isn't as wild as usual but don't you think it's a little weak?
あのさ ドラム走らないのはいいけど
パワー足りなくないか？
Ritsu?
律？
Ritsu, what is it?
おい 律！
Aw, sorry.
ああ～ ごめん
I'm just not feeling it right now.
何か 調子でないや～
Let's try it again after school.
また放課後ね
R-Ritchan!
りッ りっちゃん
Let her go, Yui.
いいよ 唯
But she--
でも…
Twerp.
バカ律
I guess Ritsu isn't coming.
律先輩 きませんね
She didn't come after school yesterday, either.
昨日の放課後も 今日も
I wonder what's wrong?
どうしたんだろ
I'd say it was because Mio has been being so cold to her.
そりゃあ やっぱり 澪ちゃんが冷たいからじゃない？
えッ？
For the sake of the Light Music Club, you need to be Ritsu's plaything for at least today!
軽音部のために
１日りっちゃんのオモチャになってきなさい
If you don't, Ritsu's heart--
でないと りっちゃんは…
--will grow hardened.
心がすさんで
Hey, mister! A jumbo!
おやじ 特盛りで
And she'll order a jumbo beef bowl she knows she can't finish.
食べきれもしない牛丼の特盛りを頼んで
What am I doing?
何やてんだ 私…
She'll be driven to despair and she'll go so far down the path of heavy metal...
そして やけになりヘビメタの道を突き進んで突き進んで
She'll never find her way back!
もう 戻れなくなって…
That's what happened to you when you got dumped by your boyfriend, isn't it?
それ 失恋したときのさわちゃん先生だよね
Pardon?
はい？
What if she decides not to come back to the club any more?
でも もし このまま戻ってこなかったら
What'll happen to our concert at the school festival?
学園祭のライブ どうなるんでしょう
Come on, let's practice.
練習しよう
ええ りっちゃんなしで？
You mean, without Ritchan?
What else can we do?
仕方ないだろ
ええッ？
But shouldn't we go ask her to join us first?
でも 律先輩 呼びに行かなくていいんですか？
You could start looking for a replacement.
もしくは 代わりを探すとかね
ええッ？
Now, I'm just saying that it's always a good idea to be prepared.
まあ 万一のことも考えとくってことだけど
But...
でも…
There's no replacing Ritchan!
りっちゃんの代わりはいません！
Mugi-chan...
ムギちゃん
Let's just wait.
待ってよう
Let's wait for Ritsu to come back to us.
りっちゃんがくるの 待っていようよ
I know she'll come. I know it.
りっちゃん きっとくるから
ああ 澪ちゃん
Mio!
Mugi-chan, you're right!
あッ ホントだ
あッ お おはよ…
Good morning.
Listen Mio, about Ritchan, she--
あのね りっちゃんね…
Look, I, I didn't come here to check up on Ritsu, I, uh...
いや 律の様子を見にきたんじゃなくって その…
She's been staying home from school.
学校 休んでるの
えッ？
Mio?
澪？
So, now you have ESP?
超能力者か
I think I can recognize your footsteps.
わかるよ
澪の足音は
How's the cold?
カゼ どう？
I still have a bit of a fever.
うん まだ ちょい熱ある
I guess that explains why your drumming sounded so weak.
どおりで ドラムに力なかったはずだ
Heck of a time to get sick, right before the festival...
学園祭の前 なのにな
You just get better quick, okay?
いいから早く治しなよ
We're waiting for you to come back.
みんな待ってるからさ
They're not mad?
怒ってない？
They're not.
ないよ
Are you?
澪は？
ないよ 当たり前だろ
Of course, not. How can I be mad at you?
It's just...
ただ…
Just what?
何？
Without you there drumming, I guess it's kinda lonely.
律のドラムがないと…
ちょっと寂しいかな
Even though you're pretty wild,
私 走り気味でもさ
I really like how your drumming is always so full of energy and powerful.
やっぱ イキがよくって
パワフルな律のドラム 好きなんだよ
あッ 律 お前…
Ritsu! Were you--
Hooray, I'm cured!
もう～ 治った！
Oh, Ritsu, you are not!
いや 治ってないから
Come on now, lie down.
ほら 寝てなって
You still have a fever.
まだ熱あるんだから
I'm going home, okay?
じゃ もう帰るな
Come on, don't go yet.
寝るまで そばにいてよ
Stay until I fall asleep, please…
ねえ お願い 澪～
Oh, good grief.
やれやれ
Excuse us. Can we come in?
お邪魔しま～す
Ritchan, how are you do--
りっちゃん だいじょう…
シィー
I was finally able to get her to go to sleep.
今 寝かしつけてるところなんだよ
Um, Why did Yui fall asleep, too?
で 何で唯まで寝てるんだ
Oh, good grief...
やれやれ
I'm back!
全快！
Now, let's bust our butts to get ready for the festival!
学園祭に向けて 頑張るぞ～！
Yeah!
おう～！
Hey!
ちょっと！
You guys didn't submit your auditorium use permission form?!
学祭の講堂使用届 出さなかったの!?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
すみません すみません
A deadline is a deadline, you know.
締め切りは 締め切りだから
Couldn't you bend the rules?
そこを何とか…
I'd like to appeal on their behalf.
私からも お願いします
They missed submission deadline because the club president was home sick with a cold.
届けが遅れたのは 部長がカゼで欠席していたからですし
Please make it an exception?!
お願いします
Well, if you feel this strongly, Miss Manabe...
まあ 真鍋さんがそこまで言うなら
You have until the end of the day.
今日いっぱい待ちましょう
Oh. Oh, you...
ああ… あんた ええ人や！
You're a good egg, ain'tcha!
Please look after Mio!
澪をよろしく
And please, while you're at it, you can look after me from now on, too, right?
そして これからは 私の面倒もみてくだせえ～
Hey!
おい
So, what's wrong with "Pure Pure"?
ねえ やっば「ぴゅあ·ぴゅあ」よくない？
Rejected.
却下
How about "Clenched Fists"?
「握りこぶし」は？
Too balladry.
演歌っぽい
How about "Gum On the Sole of My Shoe"?
じゃあ 「靴の裏のガム」
You stepped in some, didn't you?
今日 踏んだんだな
Oh! How did you know?
えッ 何でわかるの？
Mugi, don't you have any good ones?
ムギ 何かいいのない？
うん 「充電期間」とか どう？
How about something like "Recharging Time"?
えッ 縁起悪ッ
Sounds like bad luck!
How about "Popcorn Honeymoon"?
じゃあ 「ポップコーン ハネムーン」とか
Come on, guys, what's with all these silly cutesy names?
だから 何でそんな甘々のばっかなんだよ
What do you think of "Rocket Pencil"?
「ロケットえんぴつ」ってよくない？
Could you hush?
お前は黙っとけ！
God, this is annoying!
まどろっこし～！
I can't even enjoy a nice cup of tea!
ゆっくり お茶もできやしない
For stuff like this, just pick something at random!
こんなの 適当に決めればいいのよ
All done!
よしッ
She decided it on her own!
勝手に決められた
What the heck.
まあ いっか
Name! Afterschool Teatime
All Right! We've settled on a band name!
何とか バンド名 決定
All that's left for us now is to practice hard for the School Festival concert.
あとは学園祭に向けて 一生懸命練習するだけ
Maybe not...
なんだけど…
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
I am
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
So, her fever hasn't gone down yet...
まだ 熱 下がらないんだ
うん あの調子だと 明日も多分…
No.
If this keeps up tomorrow, the show is in danger.
Getting sick at a time like this just shows her lack of dedication!
こんなときにかぜひくなんて
たるんでる証拠だ
You're the one who gave it to her!
お前がうつしたんだろ
Oh, I did?
えッ 私？
Oh, Big Sis!
お姉ちゃん…
You may have fool the others, but you can't fool me.
みんなの目はごまかせても 私の目はごまかせないわよ
Finale
K-ON!